

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Mohan.ande01@gmail.com

Mobile (+91) 9834217504

Total work experience
3 Years 1 Month

#### **KEY SKILLS**

ASP.NET

Azure Fundamental

ASP.Net MVC

NUnit

ADO.Net

Visual Studio Code

Asp.Net Core

MVC

**Entity Framework** 

Azure

Angular

Web API

C#

ASP

.NET Core

.NET

Data Structures

SQL Server

Jenkins

# Komal Dhanraj Shimpi

**Associate Consultant** 

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I'm having around 3+ year of experience as a Full Stack .Net Developer. Expertise in .Net, Asp.net MVC, .net Core, C#, Entity Framework, Web API, Angular JS,TyepeScript, HTML, Css, JavaScript, SQL Server, Azure, Unit Testing, Postman, Data structure. Tools-JIRA, Git and Bitbucket/TFS.

#### **EDUCATION**

2021 Y MS/M.Sc(Science)

North Maharashtra University (NMU)

♀ B.Sc

North Maharashtra University (NMU)

2016

XIIth

**English** 

2014

2019

Xth

Marathi

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2024 -Present Associate Consultant

## **Infosys**

Working with Developmen team. Worked on Front End as well as Backend Technologies. In Frontend worked on the building UI, Services angular component, also wrote unit test cases using Jasmin and Karma Framework. In Bankend developed services for UI components using Node JS.

Technologies: Angular, Typescript, JavaScript, CSS, Node JS, AWS.

Jan 2023 - Sep 2024 Software Engineer

#### Rainbow infotech pvt ltd

I was working with development team to develop and enhance existing web application. Participated in developing new featute, new and existing bug fixes independently, production support.

Web Services

OOPS

Bitbucket

JIRA

GIT

**JSON** 

HTML

**CSS** 

#### **OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS**

City

Pune

Country

INDIA

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

Technologies: Angular, TypeScrpt, JavaScript, CSS, .Net core API, C#, Sql Serve.

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023 Software Engineer

# **Cognopi Solutions**

Worked on developing web application using ASP.Net MVC, .Net Core Web API, SQL Server.

### **Projects**

120 Days



Academic collaborative network has been developed to integrate teacher's of multiple colleges under one platform where Content/Resources will be shared on different streams. When required teachers from registered colleges can visit the site and share or download the necessary content

#### **COURSES s CERTIFICATIONS**

Net Full Stack - 6 Months Diploma Certification